# **LIZZY TRUONG**

#### DETAILS

PHONE

0401491750

**EMAIL** 

thuongb14@gmail.com

# LINKS

Github

https://github.com/thuongb14

#### SKILLS

HTML & CSS

....

Javascript

....

Python

....

Git

• • • • •

React

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

Bootstrap

....

PostgreSQL

....

## PROFILE

Proficient in various platforms, languages, and embedded systems. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Having worked in the Marketing field enables me to have a transferable skill set and be able to approach the given tasks with both creativity and a problem-solving mindset.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Web Content Coordinator, doTERRA Australia

Melbourne

Dec 2022 — Present

- Ensure the website is kept up to date by maintaining and uploading content on a regular basis.
- Support and maintain current production code. Creating, testing, and sustaining web pages by utilising CMS systems, HTML, CSS and Bootstrap framework.
- Optimise website content and UX for SEO and partner with Head of Digital and Social Media manager to execute best practice SEO.

# Marketing Assistant, Eastern & Allied Pty Ltd.

Melbourne

Dec 2021 — Dec 2022

- Create email marketing campaign and assist IT team to code email template using basic HTML5 and CSS3 via Mailchimp.
- Own, manage and implement digital marketing including strategy, campaign development, market research, content development, website & social media management to reach more target customers.

## EDUCATION

# Software Engineer Certificate, General Assembly

Aug 2022 — Mar 2023

Projects:

- 1. Wordle (HTML, CSS, JS)
- 2. **Quotes Therapy** (HTML, CSS, Python, PostgreSQL)
- 3. **Project Management App** (HTML, CSS, NodeJS, RestAPI, PostgreSQL, ExpressJS)

## **Bachelor of Business, Monash University**

Jan 2018 — Oct 2021

## REFERENCES

## References available upon request